[ Background Conversations ]
[背景谈话声]
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Hello, everyone, and welcome
&gt;&gt; 大家好 欢迎
to What's New in Swift
来到“Swift Playgrounds
Playgrounds.
的新功能”
My name is Connor.
我的名字叫 Connor
I'm an engineer on the Swift
我是一位工程师
Playgrounds Team.
在 Swift Playgrounds 团队工作
And today, along with my
今天 我将和我的
colleagues Grace and Najla, I'll
同事 Grace 以及 Najla 一起
be sharing with you some of
与你们分享
what's new in Swift Playgrounds
Swift Playgrounds 去年的大会之后
since last year's conference.
又为我们带来了什么新功能
Today's session will be broken
今天的会议将会分为
up into three parts.
三个部分
First, we'll take a quick look
首先 我们来很快地看一下
at the Playground book format to
Playground Book 的格式
ensure that everyone is on the
以确保大家的
same page.
有相同的认识
Then, we'll talk about many of
然后 我们会再讲讲
the enhancements which have been
我们为更好地构建
made to support building better
Playground Book
Playground books.
所作出的改进
And finally, we'll introduce a
最后 我们将会介绍一个
brand-new API for interacting
全新的 API  通过它你可以与
with and connecting to Bluetooth
Playgrounds 中的蓝牙配件
accessories in Playgrounds,
交互和连接
allowing you to provide a
旨在为大家提供一个
consistent user experience.
一致的用户体验
So let's get started by talking
首先 我们来讲讲
about Playground books.
Playground Book
Swift Playgrounds supports two
Swift Playgrounds 支持两种
file formats, the classic
文件格式 包括经典的
Playground file format used by
Xcode 所使用的 Playground 文件格式
Xcode as well as the Playground
以及 Playground
book file format, which allows
Book 文件格式 它让你可以
you to control the experience
管理你的用户
which your users see.
所看到的体验
Playground books are split up
Playground Book 分为不同的章节
into chapters, which are then
进一步
further subdivided into pages.
分为页
Playground books may contain
Playground Book 可以包含
resources which are used either
你在运行时使用的资源
at runtime or in the prose which
或是你向你的用户
you show to your users.
展示的 Prose 中的资源
All of this is done with a
这些都是通过
package-based file format.
基于包的文件格式完成的
If you're not familiar with what
如果你并不清楚
a package-based file format is,
基于包的文件格式是什么
essentially instead of being a
它其实并不是
flat file, it's a folder which
平面文件而是
itself contains other files and
由其他文件以及文件夹
folders which make up the
组成的文件夹
document.
的文件格式
If we take a peek inside the
我们再看看 Playground Book 的内部
Playground book, we can see
我们会看到
inside there some PLIST files,
里面会有一些 PLIST 文件
some Swift files, and a bunch of
一些 Swift 文件 以及一些
directories which make up the
目录 这些共同组成了
structure.
Playground Book 的架构
Let's first take a look at the
让我们来先看看
manifest files.
Manifest 文件
You can think of these as
你可以把这些看作是
something that's very similar to
和 App 的 info.plist
an app's info.plist.
非常相似的文件
The manifest PLIST provides
Manifest 文件中的 PLIST 提供
book-, chapter-, and page-level
书级 章级以及页级
metadata, such as the name of
的元数据 比如页的名字
the page or the icon which is
或者在文件浏览器中
used in the document browser.
使用的图标
Manifest files also specify the
Manifest 文件还会指定
options for the book, chapter,
书 章及页的选项
or page, such as whether or not
比如 是否
the live view is visible by
即时演示
default or if you want
默认可见 还是你希望
Playground logging to be turned
它在用户登录 Playground 后
on.
才启动
The other major component of a
Playground Book 另外一个主要的组成部分
Playground book are Swift files,
是 Swift 文件
and there are three different
总共有三种不同的
kinds of Swift files inside of
Swift 文件
Playground books.
包含在 Playground Book 中
The first of these is the
第一种是
Contents.swift file.
Contents.swift 文件
This is the source file with
你的用户可以与
which your users interact, and
这个源文件进行交互 并且
it's where you can store the
你也可以把
prose which is shown to your
Prose 存储在这个源文件中
user inside of special markup
Prose 是指在 Swift 文件中
comments in the Swift file.
特殊的标记注释部分
There's also the LiveView.swift
还有 LiveView.swift
file.
文件
This allows you to provide an
它让你可以提供
always on live view, which
一直活动的即时演示
provides a rich and interactive
这为你的用户提供
experience for your users for
丰富且具交互性的体验
the entire time they're on the
他们在页面操作的全过程
page instead of just when
都可以获得这种体验 而不只是
they're running their code.
当他们在运行他们的代码的时候才可以
And finally, you also have the
最后还有
auxiliary source files.
辅助源文件
These are stored in the book,
他们被存储在 Playground Book
chapter, and page and allow you
及其的章和页中 让你可以
to provide additional API
通过另外的 Swift 模块
through separate Swift modules
提供更多的 API
which are automatically imported
Swift 模块会在每个层级
at each level.
自动导入
For more information on the
要想了解有关
Playground book file format, I'd
Playground Book 文件格式的更多信息
really recommend that you take a
我强烈推荐你去看看
look at last year's session,
去年的“Introducing Swift Playgrounds
Introducing Swift Playgrounds,
（介绍 Swift Playgrounds）”的内容
where some of my colleagues go
我的同事在其中
into this in a lot more depth.
对此有更加详细的讲解
There's also really great
同时在 developer.apple.com 上
documentation available on
你们也可以找到
developer.apple.com.
非常棒的介绍文档
Let's now take a look at some of
现在我们来看看
the new features in Swift
自去年以来
Playgrounds since last year.
Swift Playgrounds 更新的功能
First up is support for copying
首先是支持页之间的
code between pages.
代码复制
This allows you to build a
这让你可以让你在构建
Playground book which continues
Playground Book 的时候
a narrative from page to page
在页与页之间维持同一叙述
while allowing users to evolve
让用户可以基于他们在写的代码
the code that they're writing.
继续演进
So when I open up a page that
所以当我打开一个页面
uses this feature, as a user, I
并且作为用户使用这个功能的时候
see a prompt to either bring
我会看到一个提示 问我
over my code from the previous
是否要将上一页的代码
page or to start coding
复制到这一页 或者立即
immediately.
开始代码
If I then tap on the button to
如果我点击
bring my code forward, then my
复制上一页的代码 那么
implementation from the previous
我在上一页的操作
page is automatically copied for
将会被自动复制
me and the source editor is
并且源代码编辑器也会
shown, allowing me to begin
同时显示 让我可以开始
coding.
编程
The next new feature is support
下一个新功能是支持
for speed control in Swift
Swift Playgrounds 中的
Playgrounds.
速度控制
This allows you to control the
这让你可以控制
speed of execution, and there's
执行的速度 并且它有
two forms for this.
两种形式
First up is support for stepping
第一种是支持在执行的时候
through code as it executes.
逐句跟踪代码
So if you tap the speed control
点击即时演示左下方的
in the live view at the bottom
速度控制
left, you can select Step
你可以选择“Step Through My Code（逐句运行代码）”
Through My Code, and then as the
然后
code executes in the live view,
代码在即时演示中执行时
the line of code, which
当前动作所对应的
corresponds to the current
那行代码
action, is highlighted in the
会在源代码编辑器中
source editor.
被标记出来
So you can see, as Bite moves
你可以看到 Bite 在
around the puzzle world, the
迷宫世界内四处移动时
line of code directing the
其中指引着当前动作的
action is highlighted.
代码会高亮
Swift Playgrounds now also
Swift Playgrounds 现在还
supports running faster than the
支持以高于默认速度
default speed if your Playground
更快速地运行 只要你的
book supports it.
Playground Book 支持
So again, you can tap on the
同样 你可以点击即时演示中的
speed control in the live view
速度控制
and then select Run Faster or
然后选择“Run Faster（加速运行）”或者
Run Fastest.
“Run Fastest（最高速运行）”
Learn to Code 1 and 2 take
“Learn to Code（学习编程）” 1 和 2 都运用了
advantage of this feature to
这个功能
make Bite move more quickly
让 Bite 更快地
throughout the puzzle world.
在迷宫世界里移动
Swift Playgrounds will now show
Swift Playgrounds 现在还会显示
runtime errors which occur in
发生在你的 Playgrounds 的
your Playgrounds.
运行时错误
So in this case, I have created
比如我一共创建了
an array with five items, and
5 个条目 然后
then I try and access the item
尝试访问索引 5 中的
at index 5, which results in an
项目 但最后出现
index out of range error.
索引超出范围
Swift Playgrounds is able to
Swift Playgrounds 可以
determine which line of code
找到具体哪条代码
caused execution to crash and
导致了执行中的崩溃情况
then highlights the line with
并且在提供的文本中
the text that's provided.
高亮显示那行代码
Users are now able to add,
用户可以添加
delete, rename, reorder, and
删除 重命名 重新排序以及
duplicate pages inside of
复制 Playground Book 中的页
Playground books, which they
它们都是在
create inside of Swift
Swift Playgrounds 内部创建的
Playgrounds, including all of
包括所有
the Apple-provided starting
Apple 提供的
points.
起始点
Swift Playgrounds is now
Swift Playgrounds 现在
localized into a few more
已经被本地化至
languages to increase its reach.
多种语言以提高它的影响范围
So Swift Playgrounds and all of
Swift Playgrounds 以及所有
the Apple-provided content is
Apple 提供的内容
now available in simplified
现在已经有简体中文
Chinese, Japanese, French,
日文 法文
German, and Latin American
德文 西班牙文（拉丁美洲）
Spanish.
的版本
And you as an author can
作为作者 你可以将你的内容
localize into any of these
本地化为这些语言中的
languages or any of the others
任意一种 或者任何其他
which iOS supports.
iOS 支持的语言
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Coming in Swift Playgrounds 2 is
即将发布的 Swift Playgrounds 2
support for the iOS 11 SDK, and
支持 iOS 11 SDK
this means that a handful of new
这意味着将有一些新的
frameworks are now available for
架构可以在
use in Playgrounds in Swift
Swift Playgrounds 2
Playgrounds 2.
中使用
This includes ARKit, CoreML,
包括 ARKit CoreML
IOSurface, PDFKit, and Vision.
IOSurface PDFKit 以及 Vision
Additionally, Playgrounds may
另外 Playgrounds 也可以
now access the camera if they're
访问相机
running on iOS 11.
只要是在 iOS 11 的环境下
You can use the AVFoundation
你可以通过 AVFoundation API
APIs to get access to the
访问
camera.
相机
It's important to note, though,
当然还需要注意
that this won't work on earlier
这个功能在
versions of iOS, so if your
旧版本的 iOS 系统上是无法运作的
Playground depends on the
所以如果你的 Playground 需要使用
camera, we recommend that you
相机的话 我们推荐你
set its deployment target to iOS
将部署目标设为
11.
iOS 11
And now, let's hop into a demo
现在 让我们通过一个 Demo
to take a look at a couple of
来看看这些
these features.
新功能
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
OK, so here I have Swift
好的 这里我们有
Playgrounds, and I'm going to go
Swift Playgrounds
ahead and launch it.
我们来打开它
And Najla, Grace, and I are each
Najla Grace 和我每个人
working on Playground books
都参与制作了 Playground Book
representing kind of our kitchen
代表了我们的厨房
where we're going to use Swift
我们将使用 Swift 代码
code to make some things.
来制作些东西
And I'm going to start out by
首先是我 我将
making a cake.
做一个蛋糕
So I'll go ahead and open up my
我将打开我的
Playground book.
Playground Book
And we're going to start from
我们将从
the very beginning by making
最开头做起
our, making some butter on our
靠我们自己制作
own.
一些黄油
So we've got this makeButter
我们有这个 makeButter 函数
function and we've got the cream
也有制作黄油
that we need for the butter.
所需要的奶油
So I'll go in and just add some
我要进去增加一些代码
code to churn that cream, which
去搅拌奶油
will then produce the butter
然后就可以制作
that we want.
我们想要的黄油了
I can then run my code, and then
我将运行我的代码
we'll see in the live view that,
然后我们在即时演示里面看到
hey, we got the cream, we've
我们有奶油了 我们
churned it, and then we have
搅拌它 然后我们就有了
butter.
黄油
So it's then, Swift Playgrounds
然后 Swift Playgrounds
is then telling us that we've
就会告诉我们 我们已经
successfully completed the task.
成功完成了任务
I'll go on to the next page, and
我将继续到下一页
we're going to use that butter
我们将用这些黄油
to make some frosting.
制作一些糖霜
And instead of having to take a
现在我将不使用
author-provided version of
作者提供的黄油版本
butter, I'm going to be able to
我可以直接
pull my butter function from the
使用上一页中
previous page.
我自己的黄油功能
So I'll tap on Bring Over My
我将点击“Bring Over My Code”
Code, and then I see the
然后我就可以看到
makeButter function that I
我之前执行的 makeButter 函数
implemented is copied over to
已经被复制
this page.
到这一页上
Additionally, the authors
同时 作者
provided a makeFrosting
提供了一个 makeFrosting 功能
function, which I'll then fill
我将直接填入
out.
这个功能
So we've got all the ingredients
所以现在我们有了制作
we need for the frosting: the
糖霜所需要的所有材料
butter, powdered sugar, vanilla,
黄油 粉末砂糖 香草精
and milk.
和牛奶
So I'll go ahead and make this
现在我要制作
return frosting, which I can do
糖霜 我只需要
by mixing together these
把这些材料
ingredients.
混在一起就可以了
Let's look at the powdered
现在我们来看看粉末砂糖
sugar, the butter, the vanilla,
黄油 香草精
and the milk.
和牛奶
And because I want to see
因为我想看看
exactly what happens to make
具体在制作糖霜的时候
this frosting, I'm going to
发生了什么 我将
enable Step Through My Code.
启动“Step Through My Code”
We'll see that we start the
可以看到我们启动了
makeFrosting function, then we
makeFrosting 函数
start to make butter, and we see
然后开始制作黄油 我们会看到
the live view update as we make
即时演示会随着我们制作
the butter.
黄油而同步更新
Look at the powdered sugar, the
我们看到粉末砂糖
vanilla, and the milk.
香草精以及牛奶
Then, we mix it all together to
然后我们把它们混在一起
get frosting.
然后得到糖霜
And so there we've completed the
我们已经完成了这一页
task on this page that we want.
的任务并且得到了我们想要的东西
So I'll move forward.
所以我将继续
And now, we're going to go on
现在 我们将继续
and start making the cake.
开始制作蛋糕
But if I look at this, there's a
但是看这里 会发现这里有
lot of ingredients here that it
许多材料
wants me to collect, and I think
需要我去收集 并且现在
there's going to be a little bit
还需要做一点工作
more work that I need to make
为制作
this cake, and I'm kind of
蛋糕做准备 但是我时间
running short on time.
有点不够了
So I'm going to pretend that I'm
所以我现在要假装我在
on a cooking show and move
主持一个烹饪节目 然后直接
straight to the end.
跳到最后
So I'll tap on this Let's Eat
所以我将点击“Let’s Eat Cake”
Cake page.
这个页面
And Swift Playgrounds is telling
Swift Playgrounds 在告诉我
me that I should go back and
我应该回去
finish making this cake, but
完成制作蛋糕 但是
because I can go to any page at
因为我可以访问任意页面
all, I'm able to tap in this
所以我可以点击
Start Cooking on This Page
这个页面上的“Start Cooking（开始制作）”
button, which will then use the
按钮 然后就会按照
default implementation of the
默认方式执行
cake.
蛋糕制作过程
So we'll see the authors
然后我们会看到作者
provided a makeButter and a
提供了makeButter 和
makeFrosting function.
makeFrosting 函数
Then, the author has all of the
作者提供了所有
ingredients needed for the cake.
制作蛋糕所需要的材料
The ingredients are then mixed
然后这些材料被混合在
together into a batter, which is
一起 调成糊状 然后
then baked in an oven, and then
被放入烤箱烘烤
we let that hot cake cool before
让热的蛋糕冷却后
frosting it.
再撒糖霜
So I'm going to come in here at
所以我可以点击底部
the bottom and just call a
启动
function to eat the cake.
吃蛋糕的功能
Because I want to go as quickly
因为我希望尽快
as possible to get through this,
完成这个过程
I'm going to actually tap on Run
我将点击“加速运行”
Fastest, which will then go
然后非常、非常快地
through each step very, very
执行
quickly.
每一步
We can see in just a matter of
我们可以看到只需
moments I have the cake that I
片刻便可以获取
was looking for.
我想要的蛋糕
So great. I've now showed you a
太棒了 我已经向大家展示了
handful of features that are new
Swift Playgrounds 的一些
in Swift Playgrounds.
新功能
Let's now take a look at how you
现在我们来看看你们
can adopt them in your
可以如何在你们的
Playground books.
Playground Book 中应用它们
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
The first feature I showed you
我向你们展示的第一个功能
was support for copying code
是在页之间
between pages.
复制代码
This allows you to craft a
这让你们制作的 Playground Book
Playground book where the user
可以允许用户
is constantly refining their
不断针对
implementation of a particular
特定函数或代码的执行
function or of other code.
完善它们
For a user, when I look at a
对于一个用户而言 当我看到
page which is being used as the
一个页面被当作
source of copyable code, I
可复制代码的源使用
really don't actually see much
我并不能看到很多的
difference.
不同点
I just see an editable area
我只是看到一个可编辑的区域
where I can insert some code.
我可以插入一些代码
But if we take a peek at the
但是如果我们看看
code underneath, there's a
它下面的代码
little bit of stuff that you as
有一些东西是你作为作者
the author provide to let Swift
可以提供的 以让
Playgrounds know what should be
Swift Playgrounds 知道哪些是
copied.
可以被复制的
That is these copy source tags,
也就是这些复制源代码标签
which allow you to tag a region
它们让你可以用标识符
of the page with an identifier,
标记页面中特定区域
which then you can reference
供你之后
later.
参考
On a page onto which code is
在代码被复制的页面上
being copied, as a user, when I
作为用户 当我
first open it, instead of being
第一次打开它时
presented with a source editor,
看到的不是一个源代码编辑器
I'm presented with the option to
而是让我选择
either copy my code from the
是从上一页复制我的代码
previous page or use the default
还是使用默认
implementation.
实现
If I haven't yet successfully
如果我还没有成功地
completed that page, instead of
完成那一页 系统并不会
being asked if I want to copy
问我是否希望复制
code, I'm asked if I want to go
代码 而是问我是否希望返回
back to that page to finish it
那一页 先把
first.
那一页完成
But I'm still presented with the
但是我也可以选择
option to start working on this
立即在这一页
page immediately.
开始工作
Once the user makes a selection
一旦用户选择了
to either copy code or use the
复制代码或者使用
default implementation, then the
默认实现 那么
regular source editor's
常规源代码编辑器就会
presented with a code they
出现他们
expect.
想要的代码
Let's take a look at how this
让我们来看看这个
happens in the source code
在源代码中是
itself.
如何实现的
And it's very similar to the
它和另外一种情况
other case.
非常相似
Instead of providing copy source
你提供的不是复制源代码标签
tags, though, you provide a copy
相反你提供的是复制
destination tag, which tells
目标标签 它会告诉
Swift Playgrounds the page from
Swift Playgrounds 你希望
which you want to copy as well
从哪一页复制以及
as the identifier on that page
在那一页上标出
for the range of code which
需要被复制的代码范围
should be copied because you're
的标识符
able to copy code from multiple
因为你可以从多个
sources onto a single page.
源将代码复制到一个页面上
Then, you place this inside of
然后你把这个放置在
the editable code region into
可编辑代表区域内部
which you want to place the
放在你希望将
copied code.
复制代码放置的地方
There's also a little bit of
另外还有一些东西
stuff that needs to be placed in
需要被放置在
the manifest file to support
Manifest 文件中以支持
copying code between pages.
页面间的复制代码
So there are a couple of keys,
这里有一些相关的 Key
the ready to copy instructions
ReadyToCopyInstructions
and the not ready to copy
和
instructions.
NotReadyToCopyInstructions
These refer to markup text,
这些指的是标记文本
which is shown with Swift
它们在 Swift Playgrounds 中显示
Playgrounds is either ready to
要么是复制已就绪
copy because the user has
因为用户已经
successfully completed the
成功地完成了
previous page or when it's not
之前的页面 要么是
ready to copy because the user
复制未就绪 因为用户
hasn't yet finished the page.
还未完成页面
And you're able to provide the
你可以提供相应的
text that makes sense for your
适用于你的 Playground Book
playground book to tell the user
的文本来告诉用户
what they should be doing here.
他们在这里应该怎么操作
There are also a handful of
另外还有一些
optional keys -- the
可选 Key 比如
CopyCommandButtonTitle key, the
CopyCommandButtonTitle
NavigateCommandButtonTitle key,
NavigateCommandButtonTitle
and the
以及
DefaultCommandButtonTitle.
DefaultCommandButtonTitle
These all refer to the titles of
这些标题指的是
the buttons so that you can
那些你可以
customize them to your
在你的 Playground Book 里面进行
Playground book.
自定义的按钮
It's worth noting, though, that
需要注意的是
if you don't provide any of
如果你不提供以上 Key 中的任意一个
these keys, Swift Playgrounds
Swift Playgrounds
will use a default title
将选择使用
instead.
默认标题
It's not possible to hide any of
在用户界面里面
these buttons in the UI.
不可能隐藏这些按钮中的任何一个
The other feature, which I
另外一个我向你们
showed you, was support for
展示过的功能
controlling the speed of
是控制 Playgrounds 中的
execution in Playgrounds.
执行速度
Swift Playground now supports
Swift Playground 现在支持
both stepping through code as
逐句运行代码和
well as running faster than the
以比默认速度更快的速度
default.
运行
The Step Through My Code mode as
“Step Through My Code（逐句运行代码）”模式以及
well as its sibling, Step
它的兄弟“Step
Slowly, is enabled for all
Slowly（慢速逐句运行）” 在所有的 Playground 中
Playgrounds.
均可用
This is because users should
因为用户基本都会需要
always be able to enable this
利用这种
mode to see what's happening in
模式来观察
their code.
他们的代码的执行情况
Run Faster and Run Fastest,
但是对于“加速运行”和“最高速运行”这两种功能
however, we can't enable those
并不是在默认能够
by default because not all
启用的 因为不是所有情况下
Playground books can actually
都真的可以
run faster.
加速运行
Some operations, you just can't
有一些操作 你就是没有办法
make it go faster.
让它加速运行
So Playground pages in books may
所以 Playground Book 中的页可以
opt into run faster or in
选择是否使用加速运行或者
running fastest.
最高速运行功能
Let's take another look at how
我们再看一下
Step Through My Code works.
“Step Through My Code”是如何操作的
So when the user taps on the
所以当用户点击
run, the speed control, rather,
速度控制 Key
and selects Step Through My
然后选择“Step Through My
Code, then their, the code runs
Code” 那么代码将会
normally, but the line of code
正常运行 但是正在运行的那行代码
which is running is highlighted
将会在左侧
on the left.
被高亮标出
Let's see how this works under
现在我们来看看这个
the hood.
在底层是怎么运作的
So if you have in your
所以如果你的
Playground book some
Playground Book 里有一些
straight-line code that's
直线代码在
running synchronously like this
像这样同步运行
where we create a string,
我们创建一个字符串
iterate over each character of
遍历字符串中的每个字符
the string, and then print it
然后把它打印出来
out, there's actually nothing
实际上你不需要
that you need to do.
做任何事
Swift Playgrounds will
Swift Playgrounds 会
automatically insert delays so
自动插入延迟以保证
that every visible line of code
每行可见代码
takes an appreciable amount of
都可以有可感知的时间
time so this code will highlight
以保证代码可以
correctly.
正确地高亮显示
There is one case which needs
有一种情况需要
some special care, and that's if
特别注意 即
you as a Playground book author
你作为 Playground Book 的作者
are providing asynchronous API
为你的用户提供的是异步 API
to your users, which under the
也就是说 它在底层是
hood is actually implemented
异步
asynchronously.
执行的
So in this case, we have a
在这种情况下 我们有
moveForward function, which is
moveForward 函数 它可以
going to just schedule some work
把一些工作
on a background queue.
放在后台排队
While this would be a good
这在应用程序里面可能是一个
practice in an app, it's not so
好的做法 但是在
great for a Playground because
Playground 里面并不是那么好 因为
when you -- when the user calls
当你或者当用户
the moveForward function, it
调用 moveForward 函数时 它
will only be highlighted for the
只会在它
amount of time it takes to
安排后台工作的时候
schedule this background work,
高亮标出
not for the amount of time it
而不是在实际
takes to actually move forward.
执行功能的时候高亮标出
So instead, you need to make
所以你需要做的就是让
your functions which appear to
看起来同步
be synchronous actually be
的功能变成实际
synchronous, and you can do this
同步 你可以通过
with a little bit of code.
一些代码实现这一点
So first, at the top of your
所以第一 在你的函数
function, you can get the
的上方 你可以获取
current run loop and then have a
当前运行循环 然后获得一个
variable, which indicates
变量 它指示着
whether or not the asynchronous
异步操作
operation has completed.
是否完成
Then, at the end, you need to
然后最后 你需要
make sure that the function
确保这个函数一直
doesn't exit until the
运行到
asynchronous operation has
异步操作
finished.
完成
So you can do that by having a
你可以这样实现
while loop which keeps the
写一个 While 循环
current run loop running until
在其中让当前循环保持运行
the didFinish flag is set to
直到 didFinish 旗标被设置为
true.
true
In the callback, after your,
在回调中 在你完成
whatever work you would be
正常回调需做
normally doing in the callback,
的那些工作之后
you need to do a little bit
你需要再
extra.
额外多做一些
First, you need to set the
首先 你需要把
didFinish flag to true so that
didFinish 旗标设置为正确 这样
that while loop will exit.
While 循环才可以退出
You then need to run a lock on
然后需要在运行循环上面
that run loop to tell it to stop
运行一个程序块让它停止
so that the CFRunLoop run call
这样 CFRunLoop 调用便会
will terminate.
停止
And then, because of how the CF
然后由于 CF API
API works, you need to tell that
的运作方式 你需要唤醒
run loop to wake up so that it
运行循环 这样它
will actually perform with the
才会执行
block that you scheduled.
你计划运行的块
The other half of speed control
速度控制的另外一部分
is support for running faster
是支持高于
than the default speed.
默认速度加速运行
Again, this is accessed through
同样这个是通过
the speed control in the bottom
即时演示左下方的
left of the live view.
速度控制访问的
The user can tap on Run Fastest
用户可以点击“Run Fastest”
if it's supported, and then the
如果支持的话 然后
Playground book does whatever it
Playground Book 就可以执行
can to run faster or run
加速运行或者
fastest.
最高速运行
Since not all Playground pages
由于不是所有的 Playground 页
can actually run faster, this
都可以加速运行
requires an opt in from the
这需要作者选择
author to enable these modes,
来启用这些模式
and that's by setting the
具体的做法就是
maximum supported execution
将最高可支持执行
speed to the maximum speed at
速度设置为你运行的
which you can run.
最高速度
If you leave this out, Swift
如果不做这一步 那么 Swift
Playgrounds will infer the
Playgrounds 将采用
default, the speed to the normal
默认速度 也就是正常执行的
speed, which would mean that
速度 这也就意味着
only the Run My Code Speed would
用户只有“Run My Code Speed”
be shown.
可以选择
But you can also set it to
但是你也可以把它设为
faster or fastest depending on
更快或者最快的速度 这取决于
the fastest possible speed you
你支持的
support.
最快速度
To adopt this feature, you just
要使用这个功能 你只需要
need to listen for a
监听一个
notification, which is posted
通知 它是一个
when the user changes the
用户改变执行速度时
execution speed.
发布的通知
That's this
也就是
playgroundPageExecution
playgroundPageExecutionModeDidChange
ModeDidChange notification.
通知
Instead of this callback, you
无须回调 你可以
can then ask the current
让当前
Playground page for its
Playground 页给出
execution mode and then update
执行模式 然后根据
animation speeds or anything
用户选择的新模式
else for the new mode that the
更新动画速度
user has selected.
或者其他的东西
So with that, I'd like to bring
关于这个话题 我想请
my colleague, Grace, up on stage
我的同事 Grace 上台
to talk about a handful of the
讲讲我们对 Playground Book
other enhancements we've made to
所做的其他
Playground books.
改进
Grace?
Grace
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; All right.
&gt;&gt; 好的
Thanks, Connor.
谢谢 Connor
I'm so excited to talk to you
我很兴奋能够和大家讲讲我们
about some of the enhancements
对 Playground Book 格式
that have been made to the
所做的一些改进
Playground book format to better
以更好地
serve you all as authors and
服务在做的各位作者
developers.
以及开发人员
The first thing that I'd like to
我想讲的第一点是
talk about is the introduction
关于
of the minimum Swift Playgrounds
MinimumSwiftPlaygroundVersion
version key.
这个 Key 的介绍
This is an optional string that
这是一个可选的字符串
will allow you to specify the
它可以让你指定
minimum app version that can be
可以打开你的文件的
used to open your documents.
最低 App 版本
Next, let's talk about the
接下来我们来谈谈
deployment target and the Swift
DeploymentTarget
version keys.
和 SwiftVersion 这两个 Key
These keys have been present
这些 Key 在
since the original release
最初发布 Playground Book 格式
Playground book format, but
的时候就有了 但是
earlier versions of the app had
在这个 App 的早期版本中
hard-coded iOS 10.0 and Swift
这些 Key 分别被硬编码为 iOS 10.3
3.0 to these keys.
和 3.1
However, now your selections are
然而 现在你的选择
honored.
更为重要
Additionally, Swift version is
现在 SwiftVersion
now a required key for you to
成为了一个需要你
fill in.
填入的 Key
This is all stored in the book
这存储在书
level Manifest.plist.
级的 Manifest.plist 中
And for Swift version, you
对于 SwiftVersion 你
should use the major and the
应该使用你编写你的书时的
minor version of Swift that you
Swift 的主版本
used to write your book.
和次版本
Swift Playgrounds now allows you
Swift Playgrounds 现在允许你
to specify subtitles for your
指定你的文件的
document.
副标题
This is another optional string
这是另外一个书级 Manifest.plist 中的
in the book level
可选字符串
Manifest.plist, and if you don't
如果你不
provide it, Swift Playgrounds
提供它 Swift Playgrounds
will just fill in the Swift
将直接为你的书
version of your book.
填入 Swift 的版本
So here in Grace's Kitchen, I've
这里在“Grace的厨房”中
used Cooking with Playgrounds
我使用了“用 Playgrounds 烹饪”
for my subtitle, and it shows
作为我的副标题 它会在
below my document in the
我文档下的
document picker.
文档选择器中显示
Next, Swift Playgrounds has
接下来 Swift Playgrounds
replaced the single Resources
替换了单一资源
directory with two resources,
目录 改成两个资源
two Resource directories,
两个资源目录
PublicResources and
“PublicResources（公用资源）”和
PrivateResources.
“PrivateResources（专用资源）”
Any files that you want your
所有你希望你的用户
users to be able to access while
在使用你的书的时候
they're using your book, either
能够访问的文件
in the file picker or the image
不管是在文件选择器中还是
picker, should go in the
图片选择器中 它们都应放在
PublicResources directory.
公用资源目录中
And any files that you don't
所有你不
want your user to be able to
希望你的用户
access should go in the
访问的文件应放在
PrivateResource directory.
专用资源目录中
Those files could be
这些文档可以是
localization files or hints
你不希望你的用户
files that you don't want your
在使用你的书时看到的
user to peek at while they're
本地化文件或者
using your book.
提示文件
Next, Swift Playgrounds now
Swift Playgrounds 现在
allows you to create specific
允许你创建特定的
runtime issues that will show up
运行时问题
in line.
并一行一行展示出来
So to do this, you can call
为了实现 你可以调用
fatal error, and the string
fatalError 它传递的字符串
that's passed in will show up in
会在行中和其他结果一起
line with other results while
在你的用户在使用 Playground Book 时
your user is using the book, if
出现 前提是如果
they ever hit it.
他们遇到这些错误话
So next, let's talk about how
接下来 我们来讲讲
you can support user-editing in
你将如何在你的 Playground Book 中
your Playground books through
通过模板页面
the use of template pages.
支持用户编辑
A new feature in Swift
Swift Playgrounds 中的一个新特性是
Playgrounds allows your users to
让你的用户可以
add, remove, rename, duplicate,
添加 移除 重命名 复制
and reorder pages within your
以及重新排列你的
Playgrounds books.
Playgrounds Book
You can see this functionality
你可以看到
already in our starting points
在我们的起始模板中
templates.
已经有这个功能
But to show it off a little bit
为了好好展示这个功能
here, I'd like to hop into a
接下来我们来看一个
demo.
Demo
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
So I'm going to go ahead and
我将打开
open up Grace's Kitchen, and
“Grace 的厨房”
this is a book that I created
这是我为
for my users to have a recipe
我的用户创建的一本 Playground Book
book on their iPad with Swift
让他们可以在有 Swift 代码的
code.
iPad 上拥有一本食谱
So in my kitchen, I have three
在我的厨房里 我有三个
recipes: butter, frosting, and
食谱 黄油 糖霜和
cake.
蛋糕
And my mom would tell me that
我妈妈会告诉我
this is not the most healthy
这可不是本健康的
recipe book, so I want my users
食谱 所以我希望我的用户
to be able to add some of their
能够添加他们
own.
自己的食谱
So if we go into the Edit
如果我们点击编辑
button, I can add a page through
按钮 我可以通过
the + button in the top left.
左上方的按钮添加一页
And then, I'm going to add a
然后 我要添加
recipe for pancakes.
一个薄煎饼的食谱
Not the most healthy, but we're
也不是特别健康 但是
getting there.
我们还是有所进步的
So if I tap Done and then I
如果我点击“Done（完成）” 然后
navigate to my Pancakes page, we
转到我的薄煎饼页面 我们
can see that I as the author
可以看到我作为作者
have provided some prose, and
提供了一些 Prose
then for sake of time, I've also
因为时间的原因 我提前
written out our pancakes recipe
写好了薄煎饼食谱
in code.
的代码
And now, when I tap Run My Code,
现在 当我点击“Run My Code （运行我的代码）”
this Playground book will
这个 Playground Book 会
intelligently generate a recipe
智能地生成一个
for pancakes.
薄煎饼的食谱
And to show you how you can
为了向大家展示可以如何
adopt this in your books, let's
在你们的书中使用这个功能 让我们
hop back to the slides.
回到幻灯片
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
The first thing that you'll need
你需要做的第一件事
to do is specify a template
就是确定模板
page.
页面
Template pages are supported in
模板页面功能可以在
the last chapter of your book,
你的书中的最后一章找到
and this key should go in the
并且这个 Key 应该存在
chapter's Manifest.plist.
这章的 Manifest.plist 中
And what I mean by template page
我所说的模板页面
is the page that's instantiated
指的是当你在你的书中
when your user adds a new page
添加新的一页时的
to your book.
实例化页面
So to specify this, you should
为了详细说明 你需要
use the TemplatePageFilename
使用 TemplatePageFilename
key.
Key
This is a string, and the string
这只是一个字符串 这个字符串
should be the value of the file
应该是实例化文件
that should be instantiated.
的值
So here I've used
在这里我用了
Template.playgroundpage.
Template.playgroundpage
Next, I'd like to talk about the
接下来 我们讲讲
difference between
以下两者的区别
InitialUserPages and pages.
InitialUserPages 和 Pages
Both of these are keys that
两者都是
store an array of page
存储一连串
filenames.
页面文件名的 Key
InitialUserPages are pages that
InitialUserPages 是
the author has created that they
作者创建了用来
want the user to be able to
让用户以如下方式
interact with in that way of
交互的页面
duplicating, renaming,
复制 重命名
reordering, et cetera.
重新排序等等
If you don't want your user to
如果你不希望你的用户
be able to interact with them in
以上述方式交互
that way, then you should store
那么你应该把它们存在
them in the pages key instead.
Pages 这个 Key 中
So here's the file structure for
这里是我的 Playground Book
my Playground book.
的文件结构
We can see that the
我们可以看到
Manifest.plist in -- is in the
Manifest.plist
chapter level, and that should
在章级 它应该有
hold the InitialUserPages key
InitialUserPages Key
and the TemplatePageFilename
以及 TemplatePageFilename
key.
Key
And then, in my Pages directory,
然后在我的 Pages 目录中
I have my Butter, Frosting, and
我有黄油 糖霜和
Cake pages, and I also have my
蛋糕页面 我也还有
Template page, which is what
模板页面 它将在
should be instantiated when a
用户添加页面时
user adds a page.
实例化
And next, I'd like to pass it
接下来 我将交给
off to Najla to talk about
Najla 来讲讲
localization.
本地化
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Hi, everyone.
&gt;&gt; 大家好
So as Connor mentioned earlier
刚刚 Connor 也提到了
today, the Swift Playgrounds
现在 Swift Playgrounds
app, along with Apple-provided
App 以及 Apple 提供的
content, is now localized into
内容已经本地化为
six languages.
六种语言
But if you wanted to localize
但是如果你想要本地化
your own Playground books, then
你自己的 Playground Book 那么
you're not limited to these six
你将不受限于这六种
languages.
语言
Localizing a Playground book is
本地化 Playground Book
a lot like localizing an app in
和本地化 App 特别像
that you have the same resource
你们都需要同样的资源
[inaudible] directories, and
目录 以及
strings files.
Strings 文件
So to localize your Playground
所以为了本地化你的 Playground
book, you're going to need to
Book 你需要
set the development region key.
设置开发区域 Key
The development region key
开发区域 Key
specifies what base language
规定了这本书撰写时的
this book was written in, and
基础语言
it's required even if you
就算你还没有开始撰写你的书
haven't localized your book yet.
也是需要这个的
If you've, if you are familiar
如果你了解怎么
with localizing apps, the
本地化应用程序
development region key is the
开发区域 Key
Playground book equivalent of
相当于
CFBundleDevelopmentRegion.
CFBundleDevelopmentRegion
So just like apps, Swift
和 App 一样 Swift
Playgrounds supports localizing
Playgrounds 支持本地化
content with strings files, and
Strings 文件的内容
there are four kinds of strings
今天我们想提到的
files that we want to mention
总共有四种 Strings 文件类型：
today: ManifestPlist, Prose,
Manifest.plist Prose
EditableFields, and QuickHelp.
EditableFields 以及 QuickHelp
Now, earlier in this session,
刚刚
Grace talked about public versus
Grace 讲到 了Playground Book 中的
private resource directories in
公用和专用
your Playground books.
资源目录
And since the strings files are
因为 Strings 文件
used to communicate with the app
也用于和应用交流
itself, it's best that they live
所以最好把它们
in the PrivateResources
存在你们书中的专用资源
directory of your book.
目录当中
So let's hop into some more
现在我们来看看
detail about these strings
Strings 文件的更多
files.
细节
So Swift Playgrounds supports
Swift Playgrounds 支持
localizing content from
运用 Manifest.plist.strings 文件
ManifestPlists using a
本地化Manifest.plists中的
ManifestPlist.strings file.
内容
And an example of some
你可以在“学习编程” 1
localizing ManifestPlist content
中找到 Manifest.plist 内容
in Learn to Code 1 is the table
的一个例子 也就是
of contents that you can see
所有练习的
with all of the exercises.
目录表
Let's take a closer look at the
让我们再仔细看看
first exercise in Learn to Code
“学习编程” 1 中的第一个练习
1, which is called Issuing
也就是“发出命令”
Commands, and here it is in
这是它的
simplified Chinese.
简体中文形式
So Playground book has a
Playground Book 在每一个级别
ManifestPlist at every level --
都有 Manifest.plist
at the book level, chapter
在书级 章级
level, and page level.
以及页级
Information about an exercise's
有关练习标题
title is pulled from the page
的信息在页级的
level ManifestPlist, and here's
Manifest.plist 中 这是
the page level ManifestPlist for
“发出命令”练习的
the Issuing Commands exercise.
页级 Manifest.plist
You can see that there's a key
你们可以看到有一个 Key
called Name, and its value is
叫作 Name 它的值是
the title.
标题
The simplified Chinese title for
“发出命令” 的
Issuing Commands is pulled from
简体中文标题
the simplified Chinese
来自简体中文版的
ManifestPlist.strings file.
Manifest.plist 这个 Strings 文件
And here you can see that the
你们可以看到
name is defined as a simplified
它是以简体中文的
Chinese of Issuing Commands.
“发出命令”命名的
So Playground markup blocks are
所以 Playground 的标记块
also supported.
也是支持的
You can also localize Playground
你也可以在 Swift Playgrounds
markup blocks in Swift
中本地化 Playground 标记块
Playgrounds using a
需要使用
Prose.strings file at the page
页级的
level.
Prose.strings 文件
And here's some prose from
这是 “发出命令”
Issuing Commands that's been
中被本地化为德文
localized into German.
的一些 Prose
To do this, in the
为此 你需要在
Contents.swift file, it
Contents.swift 文件中
specifies a block of localized
用本地化标签
prose using a localized tag,
指定本地化 Prose 的块
which takes a key.
这需要一个 Key
This key is then defined in the
然后这个 Key 在
German Prose.strings file as the
德文 Prose.strings 文件中指定为
German translation of our prose.
Prose 的德文本地化
You can also localize editable
你也可以对 Swift Playgrounds 的
fields in Swift Playgrounds by
可编辑区域
using an EditableFields.strings
用 EditableFields.strings 文件
file.
进行本地化
An example of an editable field
在“学习编程” 1 中的
in Learn to Code 1 is that Tap
可编辑区域的例子有 点击
to enter code string that you
进入代码字符串时
see in some exercises.
你看到的一些练习
And here it is in French.
这是它的法文版本
So in the Contents.swift file,
在 Contents.swift 文件中
it specifies an editable field
它用可编辑代码标签
with an editable code tag that
制定了可编辑领域
takes the key that's the
而这需要一个 Key 也就是
placeholder that we want to
我们想要本地化的
localize.
占位符
In our case, the placeholder is
在我们这种情况下 占位符叫做
called Tap to enter code.
“点击以输入代码”
That placeholder is then defined
然后那个占位符
in the EditableField.strings
在法文的 EditableField.strings
file for French as the French
文件中被定义
translation of Tap to enter
“点击以输入代码”的
code.
法文本地化
So in Swift Playgrounds 2.0,
周一你们将获得 Swift Playgrounds 2.0
which you got a beta of on
的 Beta 版本
Monday, you can localize API
你们可以对 API 文件
documentation.
进行本地化
And here's an example of some
以下是一些来自
API documentation from Learn to
“学习编程” 1 中的API
Code 1.
文档示例
It's a move forward command that
它是一个向前移动指令
you can use to move Bite in its
用它你们可以让 Bite 在
little world.
它的小世界里移动
To localize your API
要本地化你们的 API
documentation, you can use a
文件 你们可以使用
QuickHelp.strings file.
QuickHelp.strings 文件
In you AuxiliarySources file for
在针对练习的 AuxiliarySources 文件中
your exercise, it specifies a
它用本地化 Key
block of localized documentation
指定了本地化文档
by using a localization key.
的块
That key is then defined in the
那个 Key 然后在
QuickHelp.strings file.
QuickHelp.strings 文件中被定义
In our case, our documentation
在我们这个情况下 我们的文件是
is in English, so this is the
英文的
QuickHelp.strings file for
QuickHelp.strings 文件
English.
也是英文的
So along with using strings
所以除了可以使用 Strings
files to localize your
文件本地化你的
Playground books, you can use a
Playground Book 你还可以使用
Hints.plist to localize default
Hints.plist 本地化默认
hints.
提示
Here's an example of a hint from
下面是一个“发出命令”中的
Issuing Commands that's been
被本地化为日文的
localized into Japanese.
提示文件的例子
So Issuing Commands only has one
“发出命令”只有一个
hint.
提示
So in our Hints.plist for
所以在日文版 Hints.plist 文件中
Japanese, we have one entry that
有一条
represents our one hint, and its
代表那一条提示
value is the Japanese
它的值是我们的提示的
translation of our hint.
日文本地化
So the localization support in
所以 Swift Playgrounds 中的
Swift Playgrounds allows you to
本地化支持可以让你们
create really detailed and
真正地为更广泛的受众
immersive Playground books for a
创建详细的 沉浸式的
larger audience, and we're super
Playground Book 我们都非常
excited to see all of the
期待并且兴奋看到
Playground books that you
你们本地化的
localize.
Playground Book
If you want more information
如果你们想要了解有关
about how to localize your
如何本地化你的
Playground books, we have a
Playground Book 的更多信息 今天晚点
session later today on
我们还有另外一个主题为
Localizing Content for Swift
“Localizing Content for Swift Playgrounds（本地化
Playgrounds at 3:10.
Swift Playgrounds中的内容）”的会议 时间是 3:10
So let's switch gears and talk
现在我们换一个话题 谈谈
about the PlaygroundBluetooth
PlaygroundBluetooth API
API, which is in Swift
它在 Swift
Playgrounds 1.5, which shipped
Playgrounds 1.5 中 将于
on Monday.
周一发布
So Swift Playgrounds provides
Swift Playgrounds 提供
full access to CoreBluetooth,
对 CoreBluetooth 的完全访问
which allows you to integrate
它让你可以将
accessories into your Playground
各种配件整合到你的 Playground
books.
Book 中
And if you've taken a look at
如果你去看看
some of the accessory Playground
Playground Book 的一些配件
books available, you'll notice
你会发现
that they all have a really
他们都有非常棒
great and consistent Playground
并且一致的 Playground
book experience.
Book 体验
And the Playground book API
并且 Playground Book API
allows you to integrate that
让你可以把这种
experience into your own
体验整合到你自己的
Playground books.
Playground Book 中
So there are two main components
PlaygroundBluetooth 结构有两种
of the PlaygroundBluetooth
主要的
framework.
组件
The first is the
第一种是
PlaygroundBluetooth Central
PlaygroundBluetooth Central Manager
Manager, which is responsible
它负责
for all the logic to interact
与配件交互及管理它们
and manage accessories.
所需的所有逻辑
The second is the
第二种是
PlaygroundBluetooth Connection
PlaygroundBluetooth Connection View
View, which allows you to
它让你可以
customize a user interface that
自定义一个用户交互界面
users use to interact with
供用户与配件
accessories.
交互用
They both have their own
它们都有自己的
delegates, and the
委托
PlaygroundBluetooth Connection
PlaygroundBluetooth Connection View
View has a PlaygroundBluetooth
具有 PlaygroundBluetooth Connection View
Connection View data source that
数据源 可以提供
provides specific information
有关配件的
about an accessory.
详细信息
So the PlaygroundBluetooth
PlaygroundBluetooth
Central Manager provides an
Central Manager 提供一个
interface for connecting to and
与配件连接
interacting with accessories.
和交互的界面
It's really similar to
它和
CoreBluetooth's
CoreBluetooth 的
CBCentralManager, so if you've
CBCentralManager 非常相似 所以如果你
implemented that before in a
曾经在 Playground 里面执行过它
Playground, then you could reuse
那么你可以在这里
code here.
重复使用那个代码
The Central Manager can take an
Central Manager 可以使用
array of accessory UUIDs to
一系列 UUID 来
search for, or you can specify
搜索 或者你可以指定
to search for all accessories in
搜索附近范围内的
the vicinity.
所有配件
The PlaygroundBluetoothCentral
PlaygroundBluetoothCentral
ManagerDelegate has methods for
ManagerDelegate 能够和
interacting with accessories,
附件进行交互
such as connecting to and
比如连接配件以及
disconnecting from accessories.
断开连接
So the PlaygroundBluetooth
PlaygroundBluetooth
ConnectionView provides an
Connection View 提供了一个
interface for displaying the
展示配件连接
connection status of accessories
状态的界面
and allows users to discover,
它可以让用户去发现
connect to, and disconnect from
连接 以及
accessories.
断开连接配件
Here's an example of a
这是一个
Connection View that I've
我已经自定义的 Connection View
customized because my Playground
因为我的 Playground
book searches for a Bluetooth
Book 在搜寻一个蓝牙
printer.
打印机
The PlaygroundBluetooth
PlaygroundBluetooth
ConnectionViewDelegate has
ConnectionViewDelegate
methods for customizing the UI
可以自定义用户界面
and handling user interactions.
以及处理用户交互
For example, you can use the
例如 你可以使用
titleFor delegate method to
titleFor 方法
customize the Connection button.
自定义连接按钮
In my case, I've customized it
在我这个情况下 我将它设置为
to say Select Printer.
“Select Printer（选择打印机）”
Lastly, the PlaygroundBluetooth
最后 PlaygroundBluetooth
ConnectionViewDataSource is a
ConnectionViewDataSource 是一个
protocol that's adopted by the
Connection View 采用的协议
Connection View that provides
它可以提供
specific information about an
有关配件的
accessory.
具体信息
In my case, the data source
在我的例子中 数据源
provides information about my
提供了有关我的
printer, its title, which is
打印机的信息 也就是
Najla's Printer, and that cute
Najla 的打印机 就是那个在它左边的
printer icon that's to its left.
可爱的图标
You can provide this information
你可以用它的一种方法
using its one method.
提供这个信息
So let's hop into a quick demo
现在我们来看一个
of the PlaygroundBluetooth
有关操作中的 PlaygroundBluetooth 结构
framework in action.
的 Demo
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
So earlier today you saw Grace
刚刚你们看到 Grace
create a Playground page for
创建了一个 Playground 页来
making pancakes, and I love
制作薄煎饼 我非常喜欢
pancakes a lot, but I cannot
薄煎饼 但是我不会
cook.
做饭
So what I would really like to
所以我非常
do is I would like this
希望的是 这个 Playground
Playground book, in addition to
不仅仅能
generating the recipe, to be
生成食谱
able to connect to a Bluetooth
它还能连接到蓝牙
printer so that I can print it
打印机 这样我就可以把食谱
out and then give it to someone
打印出来 然后把它交给另外一个
when I want them to make
可以为我制作
pancakes for me.
薄煎饼的人
So let's go into my Playground
所以让我们进入我的
book.
Playground Book
And what I've done is I've taken
我所做的是直接把
Grace's Pancakes page and I've
Grace 的薄煎饼页拿过来 然后
integrated this cute, little
连接这个可爱的 小小的
Bluetooth printer.
蓝牙打印机
So when I tap on Connect
当我点击“Connect Printer”
Printer, it's going to search
的时候 它将寻找
for my printer.
我的打印机
And in addition to being able to
除了可以
generate this recipe, when I
生成食谱外 当我
select Najla's Printer, it's
选择 Najla 的打印机的时候 它将
going to print out the recipe.
打印出这个食谱
So keep an eye on the printer
大家好好看着打印机
and cross your fingers.
希望我能够成功
Here we go.
成功了
Yeah!
耶
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
OK.
好的
All right.
太棒了
Nailed it.
我成功做到了
So, [laughs] so now, I have the
所以现在 我有了
recipe for pancakes and I can
薄煎饼的食谱 我可以
give it to Connor after this
在这个会议之后 把它
session.
交给 Connor
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
So we talked about a lot today.
今天我们讲了很多
You got an overview of all of
大家可以总体了解
the format changes that have
做过去一年所做的
happened in the past year.
格式修改
You learned how to integrate
你们知道了如何把
copy code forward into your
隔页粘贴代码添加到你们的
Playground books so that you can
Playground Book 中 这样你们就可以
create a really nice narrative,
创建非常漂亮的叙述
how to create interesting user
知道了如何创建有意思的 用户
editable books so that users can
可编辑的书 这样用户
then modify your template pages,
可以基于你的目标页面进行修改
how to localize your Playground
还知道了如何本地化你的 Playground
books, and finally, how to
Book 最后
integrate accessories into your
如何把配件整合到你的
Playground books.
Playground Book 中
For more information about this
想了解有关这个环节的更多信息
session, please visit
请访问
developer.apple.com.
developer.apple.com
There are also a few related
还有一些其他的相关环节
sessions that you can visit or
大家可以参加或者
watch online.
在线观看
Thank you for watching our
谢谢你们来参加我们的
session, and we hope that you
会议 我们希望你们
enjoy the rest of the
也能够喜欢大会的
conference.
其他部分
[ Applause ]
[掌声]